{
    "id": "3d8de39bd8244b81a1385ce935c69178",
    "title": "Both, Either Or Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "............................. of us were ill so we didn't go to work.",
            "description": "Both is used in affirmative clauses to speak of two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "426674c80c2f4e3e97979942ecaba671"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has eaten .............................. of the chops.",
            "description": "Both means one and the other.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e894c7af92a4869b4b0400b0420e7fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't like .................................. of the colors.",
            "description": "Either means one or the other.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9640726ec9ac466b97486144fc6d9d7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I liked ................................. colors.",
            "description": "Both means one and the other.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ccf2c055b44e44a092f7a69a412b60ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited ................................ of them.",
            "description": "Both means one and the other.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4deb1b3f5bd1440d847cdee825292e1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have not invited .................................... of them.",
            "description": "Instead of writing both ...not, we use not either or neither.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8f04266ca03b48b9940a399a9a78ba86"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. key opens the door.",
            "description": "We use neither before a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "288b8eb675c84ba5909de2ba044c50ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "I could not choose between them - I liked them ...........................",
            "description": "Both means one and the other.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f265921031946749ae0e047aa5595a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. Mark nor Samuel passed the test.",
            "description": "We neither before nor.",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3649bcc1eaf240fa9fe1fb0f66f2e030"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ................................ liked the movie.",
            "description": "Both means one and the other.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f0279f3c7434ec7b6eaddefcbdcf483"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................... sings and dances.",
            "description": "We use both before and.",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c4a7ee2e568e4987a8d5c8805042bbed"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ..................................... sings nor dances.",
            "description": "We use neither before nor.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7339088aef4451c8ca6f5aecb97daa1"
        }
    ]
}